(Sheldon:)and now you think you may
have lost her love forever.
(Sheldon:)How does this compare to me being
forced to relax for a few days?
-It doesn't!
-Thank you!
(Leonard:)I'm gonna go talk to Penny.
(Sheldon:)I'm going to go inside,
put on my coziest pajamas,
(Sheldon:)curl up with a good book and wait
for this nightmare to be over.
(Sheldon:)Penny.
(Sheldon:)Sorry.
(Sheldon:)-Hi.
-Hey.
(Penny:)Look, I'm sorry I
didn't text you back.
(Penny:)I just needed
some time to think.
(Leonard:)-Okay.
-Here. Come in.
(Leonard:)Look, if you want
to break up, just say it.
(Sheldon:)-Leonard--
-No, no, no. I take it back.
(Leonard:)Don't say it.
Just hate me, but stay with me.
(Leonard:)It worked for my parents.
(Penny:)Listen, I don't want
to break up with you.
(Leonard:)Oh. Okay.
(Leonard:)Good, good.
(Leonard:)So it's cool if I cry a little?